{
    "id": "2d91f6378ac64312bb753caebe2a8f03",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We will cancel the trip ……………………….. it rains.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "638782a3430d4f50b88aff4ee20bc28f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will not cancel the trip …………………………. it rains.",
            "description": "Even if refers to future. Even if means no matter what.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "even if",
                "even though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "698a686e4c1b4a99b8a9d2dce24e608d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was acquitted …………………………… he was guilty.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "because",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cdf1e2bce30744fe852bd63ca2029184"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was freed ………………………….. he was innocent.",
            "description": "Because expresses the reason for something.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "because",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd5fe62f80d644cbb2bdd1f1c21d1b07"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no doubt ………………………… the earth moves around the sun.",
            "description": "That is used to introduce a noun clause.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "as",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ec08cc71736e42d48d32a26107d87839"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not get the job …………………………. you deserve it.",
            "description": "Unless means if not.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c44518370e0942dc9564f0292d99c9e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his balance …………………………… fell off the ladder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f75852dbbe7240db83076afe39095614"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is richer ………………………. I am.",
            "description": "Richer is a comparative expression use than after it.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "compared to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "818b7b6d9a6d40a6873a81c92ccfce57"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will never succeed …………………………. you try.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if not",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0880503b5808491c86dafe403bb25a95"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I were you, I wouldn’t tolerate this.",
            "description": "If is used to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e2d372d66a4941d1ad201e74fd315c3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Make hay …………………………. the sun shines.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "while",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7a7c8c4449844e21aef49bc92e3846a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I trust him ………………………… he is honest.",
            "description": "For can mean because.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "440207f4f5664aea94f586abef659104"
        }
    ]
}